“奇迹技巧”：听实际发出来的声音，而不是你以为自己听到的声音。
The Miracle Technique Listen for the actual sounds, not what you think they
正如你在第一章看到的，纯粹声音和
are. As you saw in Chapter 1, there's a difference between pure sound and
拼写之间有区别；要重新找回长期失去的听音能力。
spelling, regaining long-lost listening skills. The trouble with starting accent
在你已经懂很多英语之后再开始口音训练，麻烦就在于你知道得太多了。
training after you know a great deal of English is that you know a great deal
你对英语有很多预设，而且不幸的是，
about English. You have a lot of preconceptions and, unfortunately,
关于英语声音有误解。孩子可以学会任何语言。
misconceptions about the sound of English. A child can learn any language. Every
每种语言的声音都存在于每个孩子的听觉能力中。
sound of every language is within every child. So what happens with adults? People
他们学会母语后，就不再去听那些自己从没听到过的声音。
learn their native language and stop listening for the sounds they never hear.
然后他们就失去了听见这些声音的能力。后来，当你学习外语时，
Then they lose the ability to hear those sounds. Later, when you study a foreign
你学会了很多拼写规则，让你走得更远。
language, you learn a lot of spelling rules that take you still further away
也就是那门语言的真实声音；在这里，就是英语。
from the real sound of that language, in this case, English. What we're going to do
很多时候，你听过母语者的说法，
here is teach you to hear again. So many times you've heard what a native speaker
翻译成你自己的口音，然后用你的口音重复。
said, translated it into your own accent, and repeated it with your accent. Why?
因为你知道怎么说。
Because you knew how to say it.